has a lot of momentum, both in early breast cancer and metastatic breast cancer. And given
our global launches, we're starting to see a pickup in the ex-U.S. markets. So focusing in
on the U.S., you can see our NBRX share now in the early breast cancer setting is very strong,
65% plus 2% now versus prior quarter.
In addition, in metastatic breast cancer, we have 47% NBRX and 41% PRX. So taken together,
we're in a very strong position in metastatic and early breast cancer. And when we look at that data
in more detail, we see that Cascali has a strong position, not only in the overlapping segment with
our competitor in early breast cancer, but also in our unique segment, particularly the node one
high risk and the node zero high risk patients. And going forward, our focus will be very much
continuing to expand Cascali's utilization in those early breast cancer populations.
Now turning to the ex-U.S., I think one of the markets that we're keenly focused on is
our performance in Germany, where we saw outstanding performance in quarter one,
you can see in early breast cancer, our shares are approaching 80% now in Germany.
Overall, we were growing 50% in constant currencies in the first quarter. We have
continued metastatic breast cancer leadership across our key markets.
with 50% NBRX share and we also see growth accelerating now as we have more
EBC launches across a range of markets 69 countries and were reimbursed now in
40 of those markets some of the other markets we were paying close attention
to in the UK we have 78% early breast cancer and we have a strong early start
in China where we do have now NRDL listings so looking ahead
Cascale is a brand we expect to have continued strong momentum over the
course of this year so turning the slide seven because since I had also a
solid quarter 26% growth ahead of both the MS and B cell market in the US we
saw 21 percent TRX growth first prior year that was two points ahead of the
market and 1.5 points B cell class share I increased first prior year importantly
when we look at our NBRX market share both in the overall market we reach 17
percent and the B cell class we reached 20
percent so we're gaining our B cell class competitors as well as the older
drugs that still nearly the majority of patients are taking in the US overall we